<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Scrolling Text</string>
    <string name="article_title">Tupac Shakur</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle">Dear Mama</string>
    <string name="article_text">
        For more lyrics, visit www.azlyrics.com
        \nWhen I was young, me and my mama had beef
\n17 years old, kicked out on the streets
\nThough back at the time I never thought I\'d see her face
\nAin\'t a woman alive that could take my mama\'s place
\nSuspended from school
\nAnd scared to go home, I was a fool
\nWith the big boys breaking all the rules
\nI shed tears with my baby sister, over the years
\nWe was poorer than the other little kids
\nAnd even though we had different daddies, the same drama
\nWhen things went wrong we\'d blame mama
\nI reminisce on the stress I caused, it was hell
\nHuggin\' on my mama from a jail cell
\nAnd who\'d think in elementary, hey
\nI\'d see the penitentiary one day?
\nAnd running from the police, that\'s right
\nMama catch me, put a whoopin\' to my backside
\nAnd even as a crack fiend, mama
\nYou always was a black queen, mama
\nI finally understand
\nFor a woman it ain\'t easy trying to raise a man
\nYou always was committed
\nA poor single mother on welfare, tell me how you did it
\nThere\'s no way I can pay you back, but the plan
\nIs to show you that I understand; you are appreciated
\n[Reggie Green and \"Sweet Franklin\" (2Pac):]
\nLady, don\'t you know we love ya? (Dear Mama)
\nSweet lady, place no one above ya (You are appreciated)
\nSweet lady, don\'t you know we love ya?

\n[2pac:]
\nNow, ain\'t nobody tell us it was fair
\nNo love from my daddy, \'cause the coward wasn\'t there
\nHe passed away and I didn\'t cry, \'cause my anger
\nwouldn\'t let me feel for a stranger
\nThey say I\'m wrong and I\'m heartless, but all along
\nI was looking for a father he was gone
\nI hung around with the thugs
\nAnd even though they sold drugs
\nThey showed a young brother love
\nI moved out and started really hangin\'
\nI needed money of my own, so I started slangin\'
\nI ain\'t guilty, \'cause even though I sell rocks
\nIt feels good putting money in your mailbox
\nI love paying rent when the rent is due
\nI hope you got the diamond necklace that I sent to you
\n\'Cause when I was low you was there for me
\nAnd never left me alone, because you cared for me
\nAnd I could see you coming home after work late
\nYou\'re in the kitchen, trying to fix us a hot plate
\nYou just working with the scraps you was given
\nAnd Mama made miracles every Thanksgivin\'
\nBut now the road got rough, you\'re alone
\nYou\'re trying to raise two bad kids on your own
\nAnd there\'s no way I can pay you back, but my plan
\nIs to show you that I understand; you are appreciated

\n[Reggie Green and \"Sweet Franklin\" (2Pac):]
\nLady, don\'t you know we love ya? (Dear Mama)
\nSweet lady, place no one above ya (You are appreciated)
\nSweet lady, don\'t you know we love ya?

</string>
</resources>
